<resources>
    <string name="app_name">VisitorApp</string>

    <!--the default font-->
    <string name="fontFamily__roboto_regular">sans-serif</string>
    <string name="fontFamily__roboto_light">sans-serif-light</string>
    <string name="fontFamily__roboto_condensed">sans-serif-condensed</string>
    <string name="admin_login">Admin Login</string>
    <string name="welcome_to_service_foods_auckland">Welcome to Service Foods - Auckland</string>
    <string name="sign_in">Sign In</string>
    <string name="sign_out">Sign Out</string>
    <string name="please_remenber_to_sign_out_when_exiting_the_building">Please remenber to sign out when exiting the building</string>

    <string name="visitor_guideline">
    All visitors must have authorisation to enter any area where public is excluded.\n\n
   Where required or designated, approved safety equipment must be used.\n\n
    All areas must be kept clear and free of hazards.\n\n
    Be aware of moving hazards such as vehicles/fork lifts and mobile plant.\n\n
   Follow recommended procedures for handling hazardous materials.\n\n
  Keep aisles, exits, driveways and fire-extinguisher accesses clear.\n\n
    Before entering any area observe safety signs and rules.\n\n
   Report all accidents and incidents, including near misses to the Manager.\n\n
    Be fully aware of evacuation and emergency procedures.\n\n
    Maintain an appropriate standard of housekeeping and general hygiene.\n\n</string>
    <string name="please_write_the_full_name_of_all_the_members_seperate_names_by_comma">Please write the full name of all the Members Seperate names by Comma(,)</string>
    <string name="hazards_info">
    Wet/Slippery Floors - Keep floor clean &amp; dry. Wear non slip shoes\n\n
    Electricity - Follow insulation procedures &amp; turn off and unplug power supply when working on electrical equipment.\n\n
    Sharp Surfaces - Many edges can be sharp. Check carefully before starting. Report unsafe edges to Manager.\n\n
    Traffic/Fork Lift operation - Be aware of moving hazards such as vehicles &amp; forklifts. All areas must be kept clear at all times.\n\n
</string>
    <string name="emergency_procedures_info">
    Evacuate through nearest exit when instructed by manager or on alarm \–\n\n

      Identify exits\n\n Identify managers\n\n Identify Assembly point </string>
    <string name="accident_near_miss_reporting_info">Inform to Manager immediately</string>
    <string name="work_area_is_tidy_and_clear_of_tools">Work area is tidy and clear of tools</string>
    <string name="compliance_with_minimum_standards">
    Work doesn’t impact on employee safety\n\n
    Work site is secure at all times. Hazards are controlled and warning signs are posted.\n\n
    I agree to do the work that has been authorised.\n\n
    I agree to meet the requirements above and take note of the hazard. I have declared the hazards I will bring into the premises. I confirm that I have the necessary current qualification to do the work. I will follow company’s procedures as instructed by Manager or Owner.\n\n
</string>
</resources>
